conncoll.edu 2019-05-28

# Web Privacy Policy · Connecticut College

Connecticut College respects your privacy. We have created this web privacy policy to help you understand how your information is being used online.

### How do we collect your information, and what information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you inquire about admission, make a donation, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey or otherwise fill out a form or enter information on our site. While completing these activities, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, interests and other details. You may edit or update this information by contacting the appropriate Connecticut College office or emailing [info@conncoll.edu](mailto:info@conncoll.edu).

We also collect information and interpret user behavior using cookies, small files that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow), enabling the College to recognize your browser and capture and remember your browsing behavior on our website. Our web server also logs information such as IP address, date and time of visit, and pages viewed.

### How do we use your information?

  * We may use the information we collect from you—through online forms, cookies and server logs—in the following ways:
  * To send periodic emails regarding your online transactions and requests.
  * To personalize your web experience, delivering content related to your interests and relationship to the College.
  * To understand your interest in Connecticut College as part of our admission process.
  * To administer surveys and/or other site features.
  * To quickly process your online transactions and requests.
  * To help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
  * To track our advertising on third-party websites.

We also use trusted third party services that track and manage this information on our behalf including Google Analytics, remarketing with Google AdSense, and Google Analytics demographics and interest reporting. We use these services to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

### With whom do we share your information?

The College does not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information (PII) unless we provide you with advance notice. This does not include other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or providing services to you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety. Non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### How do we protect visitor information?

Your personally identifiable information (PII) is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. All financial transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers. Should a data privacy breach occur, Connecticut College will notify you via email, mail or phone within a reasonable time period.

### How can I manage or disable information collection?

If you wish to limit the information collected when you visit our site, or browse our site anonymously, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you disable cookies, your site experience may be less personalized. Also, we honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. You can opt out by using the [Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). Learn more about Google Analytics [terms of use](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/terms/) and Google's [privacy practices](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

### What else do I need to know?

In addition to this policy, Connecticut College protects the privacy of current and past students in compliance with FERPA (the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act), a federal law designed to protect the privacy of education records. Learn more about FERPA.

This privacy policy will be linked from the College’s homepage. This link will include the word “privacy” to ensure it can be easily found. We will notify users of any update to this policy on this page.

_Last updated December 7, 2015_
